http://www.rfpdb.com/view/privacy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is our top priority. We guarantee that we will adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:
The only information The RFP Database collects from its users is their profile information.
We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.
We will never willfully share your contact information with another user without your consent.
The information that The RFP Database uses is to personalize your experience and verify your identity for use within the system.
If you do not agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy, you may not use nor access The RFP Database services.
Users cannot opt out of this information nor have it removed once they register.
Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use The RFP Database service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.
Legal Disclaimer
It is possible that Confluent Forms LLC may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Confluent Forms LLC may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
Questions or Comments
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
